
const questions = [
    {
        question: "What is the name of the caretaker that raised Clarisse, Legion, and Reese?",
        a1: "Eyvel",
        a2: "Erinys",
        a3: "Etzel",
        a4: "Eremiya",
        data: "nm",
        right: "a4"
    },

    {
        question: "Who is the first named mirage that is fought in Tokyo Mirage Sessions #FE?",
        a1: "Garrick",
        a2: "Excellus",
        a3: "Palla",
        a4: "Yashiro and Navarre",
        data: "tms",
        right: "a1"
    },

    {
        question: "What type of legends or mythology does Binding Blade pull inspiration from?",
        a1: "Greek Mythology",
        a2: "Norse Mythology",
        a3: "Arthurian Legends",
        a4: "Creepypastas",
        data: "bind",
        right: "a3"
    },

    {
        question: "Which weapon can only be wielded by Sara in Thracia 776?",
        a1: "Warp Staff",
        a2: "Caduceus Staff",
        a3: "Kia Staff",
        a4: "Aum Staff",
        data: "t776",
        right: "a3"
    },

    {
        question: "What is the name of Olivia’s promoted class that debuted in Fire Emblem Warriors?",
        a1: "Prima",
        a2: "Dancer",
        a3: "Diva",
        a4: "She doesn’t have one",
        data: "few",
        right: "a1"
    },

    {
        question: "What do these heroes have in common? Guunthra, Peony, Ginnungagap, Freyja",
        a1: "They’re all dead",
        a2: "They have an association with dreams",
        a3: "They all have versions of themselves that are considered “Rearmed Heroes”",
        a4: "They all have New Year variants of themselves (including backpacks)",
        data: "feh",
        right: "a2"
    },

    {
        question: "Which of these weapons does Eirika start with?",
        a1: "Venin Edge",
        a2: "Silver Sword",
        a3: "Horseslayer",
        a4: "Rapier",
        data: "ss",
        right: "a4"
    },

    {
        question: "What is Lloyd’s title, as a member of the Black Fangs?",
        a1: "The Crazed Beast",
        a2: "The Mad Dog",
        a3: "The Angel of Death",
        a4: "The White Wolf",
        data: "bb",
        right: "a4"
    },

    {
        question: "What was the name of the castle that Nyna tried to flee from when the Dolhr Empire invaded?",
        a1: "Castle Krakenburg",
        a2: "Castle Archanea",
        a3: "Castle Adrah",
        a4: "The Royal Imperial Castle of Archanea",
        data: "sd",
        right: "a2"
    },

    {
        question: "Which of these effects is true when Faye fights near Alm?",
        a1: "Alm’s hit rate increases",
        a2: "Faye’s crit rate increases",
        a3: "The enemy’s hit rate increases",
        a4: "Both Faye and Alm’s skills will trigger more often",
        data: "sov",
        right: "a3"
    },

    {
        question: "In which significant event did Quan lose his life?",
        a1: "Battle of Belhalla",
        a2: "The Aed Massacre",
        a3: "Atrocity at Edda",
        a4: "Miracle at Darna Fortress",
        data: "gothw",
        right: "a2"
    },

    {
        question: "Which of these characters can only be used in Trial Maps?",
        a1: "Petrine",
        a2: "Sigrun",
        a3: "Sephiran",
        a4: "The Black Knight",
        data: "por",
        right: "a1"
    },

    {
        question: "Which of these has Citrinne never offered to purchase for a character?",
        a1: "A whole stock of salt-picked fish guts",
        a2: "A freshly oiled Solmic scimitar",
        a3: "A private island getaway",
        a4: "A set of accessories just like hers",
        data: "engage",
        right: "a2"
    },

    {
        question: "What was the name of the bear that Corrin had as a child?",
        a1: "Mr. Cuddles",
        a2: "Mr. Hairy Beary",
        a3: "Mr. Pookie",
        a4: "Mr. Chubby Wubby",
        data: "fates",
        right: "a3"
    },

    {
        question: "Which weapon cannot receive a blessing from Yune during the Endgame?",
        a1: "Wishblade",
        a2: "Ettard",
        a3: "Urvan",
        a4: "Thani",
        data: "rd",
        right: "a2"
    },

    {
        question: "Which route is the only route where you can get same-gendered pairings for all of your non-recruited units?",
        a1: "Silver Snow",
        a2: "Azure Moon",
        a3: "Verdant Wind",
        a4: "Crimson Flower",
        data: "three",
        right: "a4"
    },

    {
        question: "Which of these was an idea that the creators considered when conceptualizing Fire Emblem Awakening?",
        a1: "The cast would be primarily Laguz-esque characters",
        a2: "The game would be a gothic horror and involve vampires",
        a3: "The game would be set on Mars",
        a4: "The game would involve a steampunk setting rather than a medieval one",
        data: "awake",
        right: "a3"
    },
]

export {questions}